Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Commercial Recordings Collection AIA.031.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: 78 RPM Records, circa 1903-1959; 2734 sound discs
  - Side A: Coleman, Michael, "Paddy Clancey's Jig Trip to the Cottage" Side B: Coleman, Michael, "High Level - McCormacks", undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Side A: Coleman, Michael, "The Wind that Shakes the Barley the Lady on the Island" Side B: Coleman, Michael, "The Kid on the Mountain", undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Side A: Coleman, Michael and Tom Morrison, "Humors of Bally Connoll" [105838] Side B: Coleman, Michael, "Jackson's Reel" [105840] (Decca 84189), 1925 (Disk XA78 1091)
  - Side A: Coleman, Michael with Ed. Gagan, "Green Fields of America" [108603] Side B: Coleman, Michael with Ed. Gagan, "Liverpool" [108604] (Columbia 33246-F) (Disk XA78 118)
  - Side A: Coleman, Michael with J. Muller, "Boys at the Lough" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Coleman, Michael with J. Muller, "Humorous of Ennistymon" [Matrix # not listed] (Vocalion 14322), 1922 (Disk XA78 1092)
  - Side A: Coleman, Michael with Kathleen Brennan, "Wind that Shakes the Barley" [61305] Side B: Coleman, Michael with Kathleen Brennan, "Kid on the Mountain" [61306] (Decca 12067) (Disk XA78 123)
  - Side A: Coleman, Michael with Kathleen Brennan, "Miss McLoud's Reel" [61303] Side B: Coleman, Michael with Kathleen Brennan, "Tell Her I Am" [61304] (Decca 12085) (Disk XA78 124)
  - Side A: Coleman, Michael with Michael Andrews, "Stack of Barley" [39112] Side B: Coleman, Michael with Michael Andrews, "Tar Bolton" [39113] (Decca 12036) (Disk XA78 120)
  - Side A: Coleman, Michael with Michael Andrews, "Stack of Barley" [39112] Side B: Coleman, Michael with Michael Andrews, "Bolton" [39113] (Decca 12036) (Disk XA78 121)
  - Side A: Coleman, Michael with Michael Andrews, "Men of the West" [39114] Side B: Coleman, Michael with Michael Andrews, "Lord Gordan's Reel" [39115] (Decca 12037) (Disk XA78 122)
  - Side A: Collins and Harlan, "Under the Anheuser Bush" [1742] Side B: Porter, Steve, "Flanagan's Night Off" [3434] (Columbia A383) (Disk XA78 111)
  - Side A: Collins and Harlan, "Put Your Arms Around Me, Honey" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Reitz, William H., "U.S.A. Patrol " [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 16708) (Disk XA78 125)
  - Side A: Collins and Harlan, "From Here to Shanghai" [5323-C-1-3] Side B: Porter, Steve, "Flanagan's Real Estate Deal" [7003-A-3-1] (Edison 50978) (Disk XA78 2019)
  - Side A: Collins and Harlan, "Old Grey Mare" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Collins and Harlan, "If You Saw All That I Saw in Arkansas" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18387-B) (Disk XA78 2120)
  - Side A: Collins and Harlan, "Yaaka Hula Hickey Dula" Side B: Collins and Harlan, "The Kid is Clever", undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Side A: Collins, Arthur, "Preacher and the Bear" [47489] Side B: Collins, Arthur and Byron G. Harlan, "Bake Dat Chicken Pie" [47491] (Columbia A2290) (Disk XA78 126)
  - Side A: Collins, Arthur, "Preacher and the Bear" [3146] Side B: Murray, Billy, "Is Your Mother In, Molly Malone" [3146] (Columbia A307) (Disk XA78 1094)
  - Side A: Collins, Arthur, "Bedelia " [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64418) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1095)
  - Side A: Colmcille Ceilidhe Band, "Plains of Boyle" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Colmcille Ceilidhe Band, "King of the Fairies" [Matrix # not listed] (Irish I.R. 1016) (Disk XA78 100)
  - Side A: Colmcille Ceilidhe Band, "Plains of Boyle" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Colmcille Ceilidhe Band, "King of the Fairies" [Matrix # not listed] (Irish 413091) (Disk XA78 112)
  - Side A: Colmcille Ceilidhe Band, "When Sick Is It Tea You Want" [CAL.96] Side B: Colmcille Ceilidhe Band, "Signal Fires" [CAL.98] (Regal Zonophone IZ.833) (Disk XA78 113)
  - Side A: Colmcille Ceilidhe Band, "Fairy Reel Speed the Plough" [CAL.95] Side B: Colmcille Ceilidhe Band, "I'll Marry and Won't Be a Nun" [CAL.97] (Regal Zonophone IZ.876) (Disk XA78 114)
  - Side A: Colmcille Ceilidhe Band, "Forlorn Mary" [1015-A] Side B: Colmcille Ceilidhe Band, "Making the Hay" [1015-B] (Irish I-3030) (Disk XA78 1097)
  - Side A: Columbia Band, "Killarney" [437] Side B: Avril, Charles, "Where the Silv'ry Colorado Wends Its Way" [3698] (Columbia A610) (Disk XA78 1098)
  - Side A: Columbia Mixed Quartette, "Crossing the Bar" [46202] Side B: Columbia Stellar Quartette, "Absent" [46206] (Columbia A1891) (Disk XA78 2121)
  - Side A: Columbia Orchestra, "I'm Forever Blowing Bubbles" [49592] Side B: Columbia Orchestra, "That Tumble-Down Shack in Athlone" [49593] (Columbia A6104) (Disk XA78 2326)
  - Side A: Columbia Orchestra, "My Old Kentucky Home" [387] Side B: Columbia Orchestra, "Dixieland March" [1431] (Columbia A879) (Disk XA78 115)
  - Side A: Columbia Quartette, "Moonlight on the Lake" [1801] Side B: Forbes, Miss Emma and Steve Porter, "Mrs. Hiram Offen Discharges Bridget O'Sullivan" [3469] (Columbia A379) (Disk XA78 1099)
  - Side A: Columbia Quartette, "Every Mother's Son There, Sang, the Wearing of the Green" [3907] Side B: Wheeler, Frederick, "Jolly Good Fellows" [3914] (Columbia A409) (Disk XA78 1100)
  - Side A: Columbia Stellar Quartette, "My Wild Irish Rose" [45945] Side B: Columbia Stellar Quartette, "Heiddelberg Stein Song" [46012] (Columbia A1852) (Disk XA78 116)
  - Side A: Columbia Stellar Quartette, "Where the River Shannon Flows" [46296] Side B: Columbia Stellar Quartette, "Little Bit of Heaven" [78587] (Columbia A1916) (Disk XA78 1101)
  - Side A: Columbia Stellar Quartette, "Way Down Yonder in the Cornfield" [77374] Side B: Columbia Stellar Quartette, "S.R. Henry's Barn Dance" [77386] (Columbia A2427) (Disk XA78 2096)
  - Comhaltas Ceoltoiri Eireann, "From the homes of Ireland", undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Side A: Como, Perry, "Please Believe Me" [20-3684-A] Side B: Como, Perry, "Did Anyone Ever Tell You Mrs. Murphy" [20-3684-B] (RCA Victor DJ-894) (Disk XA78 117)
  - Side A: Congdon, John and Male Trio, "Where the River Shannon Flows" [3827] Side B: Congdon, John, "Dear Little Shamrock" [3828] (Brunswick 5005) (Disk XA78 2093)
  - Side A: Conlon, Peter J., "Gordon's Reel" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Conlon, Peter J., "Paddy O'Rafferty's Jig" [Matrix # not listed] (Okeh 4323), 1921 (Disk XA78 1120)
  - Side A: Conlon, Peter J., "Henessey's Hornpipe" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Conlon, Peter J., "Happy To Meet and Sorry To Part" [Matrix # not listed] (Okeh 4322), 1921 (Disk XA78 1121)
  - Side A: Conlon, Peter J., "Scholar" [7743] Side B: Conlon, Peter J., "Harvest Home and Galway Bay" [7704] (Okeh 4264) (Disk XA78 2094)
  - Side A: Conlon, Peter J. and Joseph J. Garry, "Heath'ry Breeze" [7888] Side B: Conlon, Peter J. and Joseph J. Garry, "Medley of Highland Schottisches" [7887] (Okeh 4321) (Disk XA78 964)
  - Side A: Connors, Frank, "I'll Take You Home Again Kathleen" [S1571] Side B: Connors, Frank, "When Irish Eyes Are Smiling" [S1578] (Varsity 519) (Disk XA78 1124)
  - Side A: Connors, Frank, "When Irish Eyes Are Smiling" [S.R.1578-3] Side B: Connors, Frank, "Little Bit of Heaven" [S.R.1579] (Sonora 1069), 1910/1911 (Disk XA78 1125)
  - Side A: Connors, Frank, "My Wild Irish Rose" [SR 1575-2] Side B: Connors, Frank, "I'll Take You Home Again Kathleen" [SR 1571-2] (Sonora 1067) (Disk XA78 1965)
  - Side A: Connors, Frank, "You're Irish and You're Beautiful" [MS 465-3] Side B: Connors, Frank, "Mother Machree" [MS 465-4] (Sonora 1068) (Disk XA78 1966)
  - Side A: Connors, Frank, "Rose of Tralee" [S.R.1574] Side B: Connors, Frank, "Little Town in Ould County Down" [S.R.1572-1] (Sonora 1070) (Disk XA78 1967)
  - Irish Ballads Connors, Frank Side A: "My Wild Irish Rose" [SR 1575-2] Side B: "I'll Take You Home Again Kathleen" [SR 1571-3] (Sonora 1067) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2157)
  - Irish Ballads Connors, Frank Side A: "You're Irish and You're Beautiful" [SR 1573-2] Side B: "Mother Machree" [SR 1576-2] (Sonora 1068) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2158)
  - Irish Ballads Connors, Frank Side A: "When Irish Eyes Are Smiling" [SR 1578-3] Side B: "Little Bit of Heaven" [SR 1571-3] (Sonora 1069) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2159)
  - Irish Ballads Connors, Frank Side A: "Rose of Tralee" [SR 1576-2] Side B: "Little Town in the Ould County Down" [SR 1572-2] (Sonora 1070) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2160)
  - Side A: Conroy, Michael, "Geese in the Bog " [Matrix # not listed] (Monarch 777) One-Sided Non-commercial (Disk XA78 1123)
  - Side A: Continental's Symphonette, "Believe Me If All Those Endearing Young Charms" [S-3236] Side B: Continental's Symphonette, "I'll Take You Home Again Kathleen" [S-3237] (Continental C-5029) (Disk XA78 1122)
  - Side A: Conway's Band, "American Trumpeter March" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Conway's Band, "All America March" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18182) (Disk XA78 1132)
  - Side A: Cook, Eddie, "Yodelling Busman" [CAL.162] Side B: Cook, Eddie, "My Old Killarney Home" [CAL 163] (Regal Zonophone IZ 850) (Disk XA78 1131)
  - Side A: Cooney, John, "Clare's Dragoons" [DTB.3375] Side B: Cooney, John, "Red Hand of O'Neill" [DTB.3380] (Rex 15049) (Disk XA78 1969)
  - Side A: Couturier, Ernst Albert, "Serenade" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Pinto, Anna, "Kathleen Mavourneen" [Matrix # not listed] (Edison 50998) (Disk XA78 329)
  - Side A: Cox, Denis, "Na Smeara" [E.491] Side B: Cox, Denis, "Tuirnin Lin" [E.492] (His Master's Voice I.M.493) (Disk XA78 1129)
  - Side A: Craver, Al, "Little Mary Phagan" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Craver, Al, "Death of Floyd Collins" [Matrix # not listed] (Columbia 140627) (Disk XA78 1128)
  - Side A: Crawford, Jesse, "My Wild Irish Rose" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Crawford, Jesse, "When You and I Were Young Maggie" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 19620) (Disk XA78 952)
  - Side A: Crawford, Jesse, "My Wild Irish Rose" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Crawford, Jesse, "When You and I Were Young, Maggie" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 19620) (Disk XA78 1127)
  - Side A: Crawford, Jesse, "Mother Machree" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Crawford, Jesse, "Silver Threads Among the Gold" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 19678), 1925 (Disk XA78 1968)
  - The Crehan Family, "The Crehan Family", undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Side A: Crofts, Gerard, "Risin' O' the Moon" [GB.3062] Side B: Crofts, Gerard, "Brave Kevin Barry" [GB.3073] (Decca W.4250) (Disk XA78 1126)
  - Side A: Crofts, Gerard, "Who Fears to Speak of '98?" [81806] Side B: Crofts, Gerard, "Kelly of Kilann" [71808] (Regal Zonophone IZ 837) (Disk XA78 1142)
  - Side A: Cronin, Paddy, "Flax in Bloom" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Cronin, Paddy, "Rakish Paddy" [Matrix # not listed] (Copley 9-116) (Disk XA78 845)
  - Side A: Cronin, Paddy, "Medley of Reels" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Cronin, Paddy, "Medley of Jigs" [Matrix # not listed] (Copley 9-119) (Disk XA78 1140)
  - Side A: Cronin, Paddy, "Doon Reel # 2 " [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Cronin, Paddy, "Cronin's Hornpipe" [Matrix # not listed] (Copley 9-113) (Disk XA78 1141)
  - Side A: Crooks, Richard, "I'm Falling in Love with Someone" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Crooks, Richard, "Moonbeams" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 1371) (Disk XA78 953)
  - Side A: Crooks, Richard, "In the Wee Little Home I Love" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Crooks, Richard, "Green Hills of Ireland" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 45488) (Disk XA78 1136)
  - Side A: Crooks, Richard, "I Dream of Jeannie With the Light Brown Hair" [M 354-7] Side B: Crooks, Richard, "Massa's in De Cold Ground" [M 354-8] (Victor 1828) (Disk XA78 1137)
  - Side A: Crooks, Richard, "Mother Machree" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Crooks, Richard, "Green Hills of Ireland" [Matrix # not listed] (RCA Victor 1805) (Disk XA78 1138)
  - Side A: Crooks, Richard, "Song My Mother Taught Me" [3] Side B: Crooks, Richard, "Bird Songs at Eventide" [6] (His Master's Voice I.R. 252) (Disk XA78 1139)
  - Side A: Crooks, Richard, "Colleen Aroon" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Crooks, Richard, "Irish Love Song" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 45373) (Disk XA78 2027)
  - Side A: Crooks, Richard, "Macushla" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Crooks, Richard, "Little Love, a Little Kiss " [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 1691) (Disk XA78 2059)
  - Stephen Foster Album Crooks, Richard Side A: "Old Folks at Home " [M 354-1] Side B: "Beautiful Dreamer" [M 354-2] (Victor 1825) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2182)
  - Stephen Foster Album Crooks, Richard Side A: "My Old Kentucky Home" [M 354-3] Side B: "Come Where My Love Lies Dreaming" [M 354-4] (Victor 1826) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2183)
  - Stephen Foster Album Crooks, Richard Side A: "Oh! Susanna" [M 354-5] Side B: "Old Black Joe" [M 354-6] (Victor 1827) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2184)
  - Stephen Foster Album Crooks, Richard Side A: "I Dream of Jeannie with the Light Brown Hair" [M 354-7] Side B: "Massa's in De Cold Ground" [M 354-8] (Victor 1828) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2185)
  - Stephen Foster Album Crooks, Richard Side A: "Ah! May the Red Rose Live Always" [M 354-9] Side B: "De Camptown Races" [M 354-10] (Victor 1829) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2186)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "New San Antonio Rose" [DLA 2274] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "It Makes No Difference Now" [DLA 2275] (Decca 3590) (Disk XA78 963)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "That Tumbledown Shack in Athlone" [L 4171] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "Two Shillelagh O'Sullivan" [L 46655] (Decca 28048) (Disk XA78 965)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "With My Shillelagh Under My Arm" [L 6032] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "St. Patrick's Day Parade" [L 6033] (Decca 27478) (Disk XA78 1102)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "Oh, 'Tis Sweet to Think" [74950] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "Donavans" [L 5050] (Decca 24710) (Disk XA78 1103)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "Who Threw the Overalls in Mrs. Murphy's Chowder" [73221] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "It's the Same Old Shilelagh" [73218] (Decca 23786) (Disk XA78 1104)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "I'll Be Home For Christmas" [L 3203] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "Faith of Our Fathers" [L 3027] (Decca 23779) (Disk XA78 1105)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "Alexander's Ragtime Band" [L 4386] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "Spaniard That Blighted My Life" [L 4387] (Decca 40038) (Disk XA78 1119)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "Pessimistic Character" [DLA 1984] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "Meet the Sun Half-Way" [DLA 1981] (Decca 3162) (Disk XA78 1133)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "Just One More Chance" [DLA 1773] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "Sweet Potato Piper" [DLA 1909] (Decca 2999) (Disk XA78 1134)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "Good Night Sweetheart" [E 37285] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "Too Late" [E 37284] (Brunswick 80046) (Disk XA78 1135)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "Bells of St. Mary's, The" [L 3962] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "I'll Take You Home Again, Kathleen" [L 3898] (Decca 18721) (Disk XA78 1143)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "Sleigh Ride in July" [L 3462] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "Like Someone in Love" [L 3410] (Decca 18640) (Disk XA78 1145)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "I'll Be Home for Christmas" [L 3203] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "Danny Boy" [L 2504] (Decca 18570) (Disk XA78 1146)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "Mary's a Grand Old Name" [DLA 2446] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "Waltz of Memory" [DLA 2950] (Decca 18360) (Disk XA78 1147)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "Too-Ra-Loo-Ra-Loo-Ra" [L.3456] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "I'll Remember April" [L.3455] (Decca 18621) (Disk XA78 1960)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "Galway Bay" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Crosby, Bing, "My Girl's an Irish Girl" [Matrix # not listed] (Decca 24295) (Disk XA78 1962)
  - St. Patrick's Day Crosby, Bing Side A: "MacNamara's Band" [73219] Side B: "Dear Old Donegal" [73220] (Decca 23495) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2161)
  - St. Patrick's Day Crosby, Bing Side A: "Who Threw the Overalls in Mrs. Murphy's Chowder" [73221] Side B: "It's the Same Old Shillelagh" [73218] (Decca 23786) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2162)
  - St. Patrick's Day Crosby, Bing Side A: Did Your Mother Come from Ireland?" [DLA 2260] Side B: "Where the River Shannon Flows" [DLA 2262] (Decca 23787) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2163)
  - St. Patrick's Day Crosby, Bing Side A: "Rose of Tralee" [L 3896] Side B: "When Irish Eyes Are Smiling" [L 4168] (Decca 23788) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2164)
  - St. Patrick's Day Crosby, Bing Side A: "Too-Ra-Loo-Ra-Loo-Ral " [L 3895] Side B: "I'll Take You Home Again Kathleen" [L 3898] (Decca 23789) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2165)
  - St. Valentine's Day Crosby, Bing Side A: "Sweetest Story Ever Told" [73213] Side B: "Mighty Lak' a Rose" [73212] (Decca 23482) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2187)
  - St. Valentine's Day Crosby, Bing Side A: "You and I" [DLA.2400] Side B: "Miss You" [DLA.2840] (Decca 24255) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2188)
  - St. Valentine's Day Crosby, Bing Side A: "I'll Be Seeing You" [L.3318] Side B: "I Love You" [L.3314] (Decca 24256) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2189)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing and Mary Martin, "Lily of Laguna" [DLA 2946] Side B: Crosby, Bing and Mary Martin, "Wait Till the Sun Shines, Nellie" [DLA 2947] (Decca 18278) (Disk XA78 1148)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing and The Jesters, "McNamara's Band" [73219] Side B: Crosby, Bing and The Jesters, "Dear Old Donegal" [73220] (Decca 23495) (Disk XA78 1961)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing with Jud Conlon's Rhythmaires, "Christmas in Killarney" [L 6462] Side B: Crosby, Bing with Jud Conlon's Rhythmaires, "It's Beginning to Look Like Christmas" [L 6463] (Decca 27831) (Disk XA78 846)
  - Side A: Crosby, Bing with Les Paul and His Trio, "It's Been a Long Long Time" [L 3889] Side B: Crosby, Bing with Les Paul and His Trio, "Whose Dream Are You" [L 3890] (Decca 18708) (Disk XA78 1144)
  - Side A: Cross and McCartt, "When the Roses Bloom Again" [143931] Side B: Cross and McCartt, "Sweet Rosie O'Grady" [143932] (Columbia 15143-D) (Disk XA78 1964)
  - Side A: Crumit, Frank, "I'se Goin' From the Cottonfield" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Crumit, Frank, "Parlor Is a Pleasant Place To Sit In Sunday Night" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 19777) (Disk XA78 1117)
  - Side A: Crumit, Frank, "Marion" [79185] Side B: Crumit, Frank, "Pretty Kitty Kelly" [79198] (Columbia A2948) (Disk XA78 1118)
  - Side A: Culp, Julia, "Auld Lang Syne " [Matrix # not listed] (Presto IR 1008) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1116)
  - Side A: Cummings, Donald and Eddy Holmes, "Cock of the North" [B 39049 A] Side B: Cummings, Donald and Eddy Holmes, "Moneymusk" [B 39054 A] (Decca 14016) (Disk XA78 1113)
  - Side A: Cummings, Donald and Eddy Holmes, "Dornoch Links" [B 39032 ] Side B: Cummings, Donald and Eddy Holmes, "Punchbowl" [B 39051] (Decca 14003) (Disk XA78 1114)
  - Side A: Cummings, Donald and Eddy Holmes, "March to Embo" [B 39027] Side B: Cummings, Donald and Eddy Holmes, "Muckin' O' Geordies' Byrne" [B 39028] (Decca 14001) (Disk XA78 1115)
  - Curry, David and his Orchestra, "My Ireland: Traditional Folk Music of the Emerald Isle", undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Side A: Cushing, Richard J., "St. Patrick's Family Prayer" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Delaney, Denis, "Rose of Tralee" [Matrix # not listed] (Dance Tone AC 751) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2166)
  - Side A: Pete Daily's Chicagoans, "Chicken Rag" [6929] Side B: Pete Daily's Chicagoans, "Peggy O'Neil" [7557] (capitol 1820) (Disk XA78 2713)
  - Side A: Dale, Edwin, "That's How I Believe in You" [80063] Side B: Bernard, Al, "I Want My Mammy" [80076] (Columbia A3520) (Disk XA78 1109)
  - Side A: Dale, Edwin, "Low Backed Car" [80180] Side B: Dale, Edwin, "Foggy Dew" [80190] (Columbia 33010-F) (Disk XA78 1110)
  - Side A: Dale, Edwin, "My Machree's Lullaby" [80247] Side B: Hart, Charles, "Erin, You're Wearin' A Wonderful Smile" [80233] (Columbia A3605) (Disk XA78 2405)
  - Side A: Dalhart, Vernon, "Paul Revere" [77781] Side B: Peerless Quartette, "France, We'll Rebuild Your Towns For You" [77807] (Columbia A2567) (Disk XA78 1108)
  - Side A: Dalhart, Vernon, "Sidewalks of New York" [140795] Side B: Dalhart, Vernon, "Girl I Left Behind Me" [140796] (Columbia 437-D) (Disk XA78 1963)
  - Side A: Dalhart, Vernon, "Crepe on the Little Cabin Door" [142866] Side B: Dalhart, Vernon, "We Will Meet at the End of the Trail" [142867] (Columbia 15107-D) (Disk XA78 2351)
  - Side A: Dalhart, Vernon and Carson Robison, "My Blue Ridge Mountain Home" [Not Listed] Side B: Dalhart, Vernon and Carson Robison, "Golden Slippers" [Not Listed] (Victor 20539-B) (Disk XA78 2347)
  - Side A: Dalhart, Vernon and Ed. Smalle, "Mrs. Murphy's Chowder" [9759] Side B: Jones, Billy and Ernest Hare, "Oh You Can't Fool an Old Hoss Fly" [9758] (Edison 51415) (Disk XA78 1411)
  - Side A: D'Almaine, Charles, "Medley of Jigs and Reels" [3749] Side B: Prince's Orchestra, "Harrigan's Reel" [3876] (Columbia A1712) (Disk XA78 1111)
  - Side A: Daly, Jack, "Ireland Must Be Heaven" [CAR.5440] Side B: Daly, Jack, "When They Ask You What Your Name Is" [CAR.5441] (Regal Zonophone IZ.993) (Disk XA78 52)
  - Side A: Daly, Jack, "If You're Irish Come into the Parlor" [CAR.5567] Side B: Daly, Jack, "My Irish Home Sweet Home" [CAR.5568] (Regal Zonophone IZ.1048) (Disk XA78 53)
  - Side A: Daly, Jack, "Old Irish Lady, An" [OAR 3750] Side B: Daly, Jack, "When Irish Eyes Are Smiling" [OAR 3752] (Regal Zonophone IZ 415) (Disk XA78 1106)
  - Side A: Daly, Jack, "That's How I Spell I.R.E.L.A.N.D" [OAR 3586] Side B: Daly, Jack, "Smilin' Through" [OAR 3587] (Regal Zonophone IZ 411) (Disk XA78 1107)
  - Side A: Daly, Jack, "My Heart's in Old Killarney" [CAR.4459] Side B: Daly, Jack, "Charladies' Ball" [CAR.4460] (Regal Zonophone IZ 614) (Disk XA78 1149)
  - Side A: Daly, Jack, "It Takes an Irish Heart to Sing an Irish Song" [CAR.4853] Side B: Daly, Jack, "My Wild Irish Rose" [CAR.4854] (Regal Zonophone I.Z.817) (Disk XA78 1150)
  - Side A: Daly, Jack, "Where the River Shannon Flows Down to the Sea" [CAR.5247] Side B: Daly, Jack, "When I'm Old and Grey" [CAR.5173] (Regal Zonophone IZ.948) (Disk XA78 1151)
  - Side A: Daly, Jack, "Phil the Fluter's Ball" [CAR.5245] Side B: Daly, Jack, "Irish Lullaby" [CAR.5248] (Regal Zonophone IZ.951) (Disk XA78 1152)
  - Side A: Daly, Jack, "Mother Machree" [CAR.5246] Side B: Daly, Jack, "That Old Irish Harp in Kildare" [CAR.5352] (Regal Zonophone IZ 969) (Disk XA78 1153)
  - Side A: Daly, Jack, "Irish Emigrant" [CAR.6073] Side B: Daly, Jack, "Terence's Farewell to Kathleen" [CAR.6074] (Regal Zonophone IZ.1156) (Disk XA78 1154)
  - Side A: Daly, Jack, "Dear Little Shamrock" [CAR.6298] Side B: Daly, Jack, "Off to Philadelphia" [CAR.6299] (Regal Zonophone IZ 1230) (Disk XA78 1155)
  - Side A: Dambois, Maurice, "Love's Old Sweet Song" [] Side B: Dambois, Maurice, "Let the Rest of the World Go By" [] (Aeolian Vocalion B24014) (Disk XA78 2321)
  - Side A: Dame, Donald, "To the Land of My Own Romance" [P-172] Side B: Dame, Donald, "My Dream Girl" [P-172] (RCA Victor 20-2114) (Disk XA78 54)
  - Side A: Dame, Donald, "Lonesome – That's All" [20-2113-A] Side B: Dame, Donald, "Little Love, a Little Kiss" [20-2113-B] (RCA Victor P 172) (Disk XA78 1156)
  - Side A: Dame, Donald, "Kathleen Mavourneen" [P-172] Side B: Dame, Donald, "I'll Take You Home Again, Kathleen" [P-172] (RCA Victor 20-2115) (Disk XA78 1157)
  - Side A: Dan Sullivan's Shamrock Band, "Green Grow the Rushes O'" [B 39077] Side B: Dan Sullivan's Shamrock Band, "Leg of the Duck" [B 39078] (Decca 12045) (Disk XA78 415)
  - Side A: Dan Sullivan's Shamrock Band, "Peeler's Jacket" [B 39075] Side B: Dan Sullivan's Shamrock Band, "Favorite Jig" [B 39076] (Decca 12049) (Disk XA78 416)
  - Side A: Dan Sullivan's Shamrock Band, "Gordon's Reel" [40-1979] Side B: Dan Sullivan's Shamrock Band, "Merry Old Widow" [40-1980] (His Master's Voice B.3611) (Disk XA78 421)
  - Side A: Dan Sullivan's Shamrock Band, "I'm Leaving Tipperary" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Dan Sullivan's Shamrock Band, "Shamus O'Brien" [Matrix # not listed] (RCA Victor 26-7507) (Disk XA78 422)
  - Side A: Dan Sullivan's Shamrock Band, "Blackbird" [106363] Side B: Dan Sullivan's Shamrock Band, "Brian Boru's March" [106356] (Columbia 33527-F) (Disk XA78 437)